[
  {"id": 1, "problem": "2+3=", "answer": 5, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 2, "problem": "5-1=", "answer": 4, "type": "减法运算"},
  {"id": 3, "problem": "3-2=", "answer": 1, "type": "减法运算"},
  {"id": 4, "problem": "0+3=", "answer": 3, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 5, "problem": "4+3=", "answer": 7, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 6, "problem": "4+5=", "answer": 9, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 7, "problem": "1+3=", "answer": 4, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 8, "problem": "2+4=", "answer": 6, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 9, "problem": "3-2=", "answer": 1, "type": "减法运算"},
  {"id": 10, "problem": "2-1=", "answer": 1, "type": "减法运算"},
  {"id": 11, "problem": "8-2=", "answer": 6, "type": "减法运算"},
  {"id": 12, "problem": "7-6=", "answer": 1, "type": "减法运算"},
  {"id": 13, "problem": "8-5=", "answer": 3, "type": "减法运算"},
  {"id": 14, "problem": "5+2=", "answer": 7, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 15, "problem": "9-3=", "answer": 6, "type": "减法运算"},
  {"id": 16, "problem": "8+0=", "answer": 8, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 17, "problem": "7-7=", "answer": 0, "type": "减法运算"},
  {"id": 18, "problem": "3+7=", "answer": 10, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 19, "problem": "6+3=", "answer": 9, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 20, "problem": "7-2=", "answer": 5, "type": "减法运算"},
  {"id": 21, "problem": "2+5=", "answer": 7, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 22, "problem": "5-2=", "answer": 3, "type": "减法运算"},
  {"id": 23, "problem": "2+4=", "answer": 6, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 24, "problem": "7-4=", "answer": 3, "type": "减法运算"},
  {"id": 25, "problem": "4+6=", "answer": 10, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 26, "problem": "8-4=", "answer": 4, "type": "减法运算"},
  {"id": 27, "problem": "8+2=", "answer": 10, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 28, "problem": "6-3=", "answer": 3, "type": "减法运算"},
  {"id": 29, "problem": "5-4=", "answer": 1, "type": "减法运算"},
  {"id": 30, "problem": "9-4=", "answer": 5, "type": "减法运算"},
  {"id": 31, "problem": "10+6=", "answer": 16, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 32, "problem": "10-3=", "answer": 7, "type": "减法运算"},
  {"id": 33, "problem": "5+10=", "answer": 15, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 34, "problem": "10-10=", "answer": 0, "type": "减法运算"},
  {"id": 35, "problem": "2+10=", "answer": 12, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 36, "problem": "10+0=", "answer": 10, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 37, "problem": "10+7=", "answer": 17, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 38, "problem": "4+10=", "answer": 14, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 39, "problem": "6+10=", "answer": 16, "type": "加法运算"},
  {"id": 40, "problem": "10-8=", "answer": 2, "type": "减法运算"}
]